(Bernadette:)Don't take this the wrong way,
but how many
(Bernadette:)of these little booze balls
have you had?
(Howard:)You don't think I'm a leader?
(Bernadette:)I was kidding.
Of course you are.
(Howard:)Right. I couldn't change
if I wanted to.
(Bernadette:)You better not change,
because I love who you are.
(Bernadette:)Now, will you need help cleaning
all this up when you're done
(Bernadette:)or can you do it
all by yourself?
(Howard:)All by myself.
(Bernadette:)There's my big boss man.
(Sheldon:)So, often on the front
of the locomotive
(Sheldon:)is a large iron wedge
(Sheldon:)for clearing objects
off the tracks.
(Sheldon:)Now, while commonly
known as a cowcatcher,
(Sheldon:)I prefer the more
accurate "cow exploder."
(Penny:)Okay. Sheldon,
let me ask you a question.
(Leonard:)Mmm.
If I was
at a train station
(Penny:)and one train could take me
to my current job
(Penny:)and the other train could take
me to an audition for a movie,
(Penny:)which train should I get on?